So my project is called the quad-CAN filter tester. Its job is to test this quad-CAN filter.
This quad-CAN filter incorporates five connections, CAN1, CAN2, LIN, CAN3 and CAN4.
All of these connections are being tested by this quad-CAN filter tester,
and the results are being showed onto this PC when it's plugged in into the USB.
Which means all the results can be shown on the terminal, which is very nice.
Once I will turn on the quad-CAN filter tester, the LEDs flash onto this quad-CAN filter,
meaning that the two LEDs flash here, meaning that all the CAN connections are good.
And if I go to the terminal here, the C connections, as you can see, which is CAN1, CAN2 and LIN,
all of them are okay, and the C1 connections, CAN3, CAN4, is also okay.
These are the C, and these are the C1 connections.
So C connections are here, C1 connections are here, and the same goes for this.
Now, in order to fully test all of the capabilities of this project,
I can firstly turn off the quad-CAN filter and let's just say something happens.
Actually, the tested component is not working, and let's just remove one of these parts here,
which is the C connections.
This C little filter is removed, which means what I'm going to see on the terminal here
is that all of the C connections, the thing that I've removed now, are going to be labeled as error.
So I turn on the quad-CAN filter tester.
The same thing happens.
The only thing here is that the C connections are labeled as error,
which is what I've anticipated, meaning everything is fine.
Same thing I can do with this.
I can remove the C1 connections here,
meaning that it's basically empty and nothing is going to really work here.
And as I'll turn off and I'll turn on the quad-CAN filter tester,
all of them are going to be shown as error, so C and C1 connections.
Now, what I can do now is I can just put all of these connections on.
So I put in the C connections here, and I will also put in the C1 connections.
It's very hard to do this with one hand, but here you go.
All of them are being put in, and now my job is to turn off the quad-CAN filter
and then turn it on again.
Mind you, all of the C and C1 connections here are plugged in,
which means that all of the connections should show an okay time for each of those connections.
It shows that the test is successful, and once the test is failed,
it's going to say test is failed.
And that's pretty much it.
That is my whole quad-CAN filter tester software project.
So hopefully you've enjoyed this, and take care.